<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PEOPLE Unleashed</title>
    <link>https://people-unleashed.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on PEOPLE Unleashed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://people-unleashed.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bio Dome Homes</title>
      <link>https://people-unleashed.com/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people-unleashed.com/music/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As a family, we, Alosha &amp;amp; Zoya from Bio-Veda Academy, have abandoned our home in the final
stages of mortgage repayment. It was not an easy decision, but one that completely flipped
our lives, unlocking incredible opportunities we could have never dreamt possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&amp;rsquo;s why we have much to share about these bold, scary steps as we break through to a
new reality we are co-creating with our bare hands!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud4z2.com</title>
      <link>https://people-unleashed.com/about-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people-unleashed.com/about-story/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AWS CERTIFIED SOLUTIONS ARCHITECT&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Responsible for building and integration of computer systems and information for meeting specific needs.
Involving the integration of hardware and software for meeting the customer-defined purpose. Translate the
technical requirements of a project into an architecture and design ideal for the final product. Reducing
the gap between between complex problems and solutions.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connecting Consciousness</title>
      <link>https://people-unleashed.com/math/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people-unleashed.com/math/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Simon grew up in a family that had links to British and American intelligence.
Simon&amp;rsquo;s mother worked for Mi5, however while she was managed by mi5 she was in reality
working for the NSA.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Constitutional Sheriffs &amp; Peace Officers Association</title>
      <link>https://people-unleashed.com/typography/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people-unleashed.com/typography/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The CSPOA was started because of the huge need to remind sheriffs and peace officers about their oath of office.
Throughout America, law enforcement agencies have a slogan that defines the primary function of the agency. The slogan, which has been used for decades, yet which has been removed from the door of many police agency patrol vehicles, is To Protect and Serve.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EARTH UNITED</title>
      <link>https://people-unleashed.com/mailchimp-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people-unleashed.com/mailchimp-features/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;TOGETHER WE STAND&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you wish to be free?&amp;hellip;.. If desire for freedom from a tyrannical power structure exists while restoring peace, then Earth United is a light for our world to go. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter who or what your background or beliefs are, these are FACTS that require action as this truth affects us all once known&amp;hellip; and the time to correct and reclaim our FREEDOM , Sovereignty &amp;amp; power is now!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Ecovillage Network</title>
      <link>https://people-unleashed.com/search-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people-unleashed.com/search-page/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Global Ecovillage Network (GEN) catalyzes communities for a regenerative world. GEN
is a growing network of regenerative communities and initiatives that bridge cultures,
countries, and continents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GEN builds bridges between policy-makers, governments, NGOs, academics, entrepreneurs,
activists, community networks and ecologically-minded individuals across the globe in
order to develop strategies for a global transition to resilient communities and cultures.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green Dream Project</title>
      <link>https://people-unleashed.com/images/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people-unleashed.com/images/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re Jim and Jess, an off-grid couple building our dream of a sustainable homestead in Southern
Arizona.  What is it like to live on rainwater in a dry climate and build a huge 14,000 gallon earthbag
cistern by hand?  How can you thrive comfortably on 100% off-grid solar energy?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Handmade by Zionette</title>
      <link>https://people-unleashed.com/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people-unleashed.com/features/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Masterpiece handmade items brought to you by Zionette.  I use the finest qualities and my yarns are purchased
from Lion Brand Yarns made here in the USA.  Lion Brand Yarn was founded in 1878 in the United States. It is the oldest producer of
knitting and craft yarn in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Community</title>
      <link>https://people-unleashed.com/figures/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people-unleashed.com/figures/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;In order to change an existing paradigm you do not struggle to try and change the problematic model.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You create a new model and make the old ones obsolete.  That, in essence, is the higher service to which we are all being called.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~ Buckminster Fuller ~&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Small Town</title>
      <link>https://people-unleashed.com/other-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people-unleashed.com/other-features/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Imagine a perfect world full of harmony and abundance. The kind of world most of us have
dreamed of all our lives. This world is possible and we are creating it for ourselves –
not somewhere in the distant future, but now, in our own lifetime.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PEOPLE Unleashed</title>
      <link>https://people-unleashed.com/adirondack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people-unleashed.com/adirondack/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;“Our success is contingent upon the highest moral idea “the greatest good to the greatest number”. Aspiration, desire, and harmonious relations, constantly and persistently maintained, will accomplish results. Well-Being comes from Well-Doing”. ~ Charles F. Haanel&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mission: Rise Up - Impact - Explore&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zionette&#39;s Story</title>
      <link>https://people-unleashed.com/slides/adirondack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people-unleashed.com/slides/adirondack/</guid>
      <description>class: title, smokescreen, shelf, no-footer background-image: url(leo-serrat-533922-unsplash.jpg)
Zionette&amp;rsquo;s Story&amp;hellip; &amp;ldquo;arrow -&amp;gt; -&amp;gt; side to see slides&amp;rdquo;  class: img-caption Handmade Pieces of Art&amp;hellip; class: img-caption Shoe making by Handmade-by-Zionette.com class: img-caption Side view of shoe. class: img-caption Tweed Summer Hat Handmade-by-Zionette.com class: img-caption Hanging Soap Saver Handmade-by-Zionette.com class: img-caption Aloe~Cactus Flower boutique soap made with essential oils Handmade-by-Zionette.com class: img-caption Rose~Mint boutique soap made with essential oils Handmade-by-Zionette.com. class: img-caption Rosemary~Lavendar bud boutique soap made with essential oils Handmade-by-Zionette.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
